So this is the place?
Mm-hm.
Maybe it was a bad idea to come see it.
I'm getting kinda nervous.
Those Union shitheads outnumber us.
Hey, my man.
I'm gonna be here, so don't worry, bro.
They're all dead meat when
I get my hands on these idiots.
Dumbass.
You gonna take 'em all on? Huh?
Let's push it a few days.
Hmm?
We need to come up
with a plan so we can win.
Who's the person
Na Baek-jin trusts most in the Union?
Mmm.
Hey.
Before,
remember when you, like,
stabbed the top of my foot?
I had to get a fucking tetanus shot.
Sorry about that.
You're freaking sentimental, aren't you?
Yeah, whatever.
So you're saying
the Union has a bank account
under a fake identity? Hmm?
You think I have the account info, right?
And you want me to be the squeaky wheel.
Then what
do I fucking get in return?
You could've
been blamed for everything.
When the Union collapses,
the criminal evidence disappears too.
You'd benefit from that.
I knew you'd be a fucking psycho, hmm?
The second I saw you.
Okay.
Cool.
Where are you going?
I have to study
about Na Baek-jin and the Union.
EUNJANG (UNKNOWN) VS UNION (300 PEOPLE?)
EUNJANG IS OUTNUMBERED, MUST DIVIDE UNION
CONVERT INSIDER: CHOI HYO-MAN
Hyo-man…
…I need your help.
This fake identity bank account evidence
is from Geum Seong-je.
THIS PONK STILL DOESN'T KNOW
POLICE ARE ONTOO THE UNION
Spread this to the Union members.
NOV 19, BAEK DONG-HA, 3,115,000 WON
NOV 18, KWON HYEOK-JIN, 2,250,000 WON
Look at this.
- We're screwed.
- What is that?
- Baek-jin siphoned money.
- What?
These fucking assholes.
Oh, shit. Hey, fuck this.
Wait, this is real?
You told me
that the Union was kept together by money.
BAEK-JIN'S BURNER ACCOUMT
POLICE GAT HIM
Na Baek-jin took the money.
- Yeah.
- Let me see that, dumbass.
Na Baek-jin took the money and ran.
HYO-MAN:
YOU MORONS
- I'm fucking jealous of his fucking money.
- We're totally fucked.
ASSHOLE MADE A FORTUNE
What the fuck is this?
If money
brought the Union together,
money will tear them apart.
GYEONG-SEOK:
WE MIGHT GET SCREWED FOR THIS
HYO-MAN:
LOOKS LIKE IT
So do what you do best.
Aah!
Hey, do you think jumping rope is gonna
make you, like, stronger or what?
Your knees are bad. Shit.
I have to at least
do something to work out.
You're, like, always thinking, man.
I think you're the one
who thinks too much.
What?
You're worried about him.
Na Baek-jin.
Whoa. Hey, is this your place?
Mm-hm.
Whoa! It's hella huge and super fancy.
My house is like freakin' ant poop.
NA BAEK-JIN
Hey, a basketball hoop!
Do you know how to play?
PARK HU-MIN
Loser buys a soda!
Why are you standing there? Hurry up!
Thank you for the winter jackets.
It's kept the kids warm.
And they love them.
I'm glad.
Baek-jin-a.
You don't…
you don't need to send us donations…
every single month.
I never bother to ask
where you got all that money from,
but it's making me worry.
I'll rest and then leave.
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 2
This is all?
Those assholes all bailed on us.
Everyone's saying the bank accounts we've
been keeping got exposed, or something.
Is everything good with us?
Yeon Si-eun.
SEONG-JE: THE EVIDENCE AGAINST NA BAEK-JIN
SEEMS TO BE IN THE UNION OFFICE
LET'S GRAB IT NOW WHILE IT'S EMPTY
Hey, it's my bros!
Dang, this weather's so awful!
Why didn't you guys check
the weather report?
My shoes are getting wet.
Hey, it's always more fun
to play in the rain, you ass.
Let's go!
Where's Si-eun?
Busy signal.
Wonder why.
- He probably met up with Baku first.
- Oh!
EUNJANG HIGH, LET'S GO
BAKU
Hey, why are you guys so late?
Everybody's so tense and shit.
Hey, so?
Are you guys ready to annihilate
these stupid-ass Union shits or what?
Hey, why are you even here?
Did you forget you tried
to sell Eunjang to the Union?
- You're trying to fix your reputation?
- What the heck?
I'm just doing what Si-eun asked me to do,
to help you guys out.
He asked me for a favor.
I'm not gonna forgive you.
Every single day,
you bullied and tortured us.
You shouldn't have done that.
I won't forget it.
But we're going to need you
to help us today.
Let's go.
Oh.
What's goin' on? Why are you so early?
It wasn't that urgent.
Ah. Shit.
This is our burner phone.
The app has the entire transaction.
Everything in here is original.
You're gonna need this
to end Baek-jin, right?
Why are you always trying so hard?
If you want nobody to get hurt,
then why don't you just get hurt?
Ooh!
Relax.
- Relax, man.
- You know, it felt weird.
I almost became some kinda good guy.
Stuff like this is more fun for me.
Did you all come running
when you heard about a fight?
Thanks, everyone, for showin' up.
Where is Si-eun?
Huh?
His phone was busy,
so I thought he was with you.
YEON SI-EUN:
I'M STOPPING BY THE BOWLING CLUB
Si-eun says he went to the bowling club.
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Please leave a message after the--
Si-eun's phone's turned off.
Oh shit. You think the Union assholes
are trying to trap us?
Uh, I'll go to the bowling club.
You two should stay here.
I'll go get Si-eun, okay?
Hurry back.
Mmm.
Na Baek-jin!
If you lose today,
that'll be the end of the Union.
Understand?
Kill them all.
I'm claiming Na Baek-jin.
Handle everybody else, all right?
Okay!
Let's go!
Hey, fucker!
Shit,
how do I fucking do this?
Fuck you, man.
Fucking hell. Come here, you little shit.
Fuck!
Thank you.
Si-eun-a.
Are you okay?
How did you get here?
Come on, let's get out of here.
Try harder.
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
You're done, you asshole.
I'm gonna fucking end you.
Jun-tae-ya. You okay?
I'm fine.
We need to hurry.
I'll follow. You go ahead.
- You need the hospital.
- No, I'm good.
I just need a second, that's all.
Please go.
You need to go
and help them stop fighting for good.
Mmm.
Stay down. Asshole.
Shut up.
Hey, cut out your fucking bullshit.
Come on.
- Asshole!
- You shit!
Ow! What the fuck?
Come on, you asshole!
Eat my shit, fucker!
Oh! You stupid jerk-face fucker!
Hey, you! Hey! Come on.
What? Come on!
Asshole!
Son of a bitch!
Stop fucking around!
Hey, Baek-jin-a, you've improved a lot.
But this isn't why
I taught you how to fight.
Phew.
I'll end this for you.
It hurt, right?
Na Baek-jin,
are you all right?
Hey. Why are you always getting beat up?
Hold your fists real tight.
Don't avoid their eyes.
Hey!
Na Baek-jin won!
That's enough!
It's all over, you shits!
Na Baek-jin won!
Fucking stop fighting!
Baek-jin's won!
And now…
…Eunjang will belong to the Union.
If you…
cannot accept this decision,
then come out.
Who's next?
Shit, man.
Come out, you pieces of shit!
And then there was one.
Yeon Si-eun.
What?
You like to talk a big game.
Are you scared
to back that up with a fight?
You're the only one who's talking.
I'm here to fight.
You fucking asshole.
Nice job!
Yeon Si-eun.
Oh shit.
Baku only came for my arms.
This is part of a plan, isn't it?
My arms and then legs?
What's next in your plan?
How wide is your margin of error,
you goddamn shit?
It's still in.
What?
It's still within the margin of error.
Your limbs are all finished.
If you lose, by any chance,
I'll step in.
Get back up.
Somehow, I'll hold out until you do.
Whoa.
- Whoa.
- Hey.
We won.
Baek-jin-a.
I'm sorry.
But…
you should be sorry to me too.
The fight
is over!
It's done!
Nice!
Did you see how amazing I was?
Guys, did you see how amazing I was?
Hear me out! Hear me out!
In that one-on-one fight, I was like, pow!
And I tackled him and, yah!
I'm serious. I'm serious!
It was the coolest thing I've ever
freaking done! Hey, listen to me!
Jun-tae-ya!
We completely
knocked out after that.
Like as if we were catching up
on all the sleep we had missed.
- No way.
- I didn't say that.
- Oh my gosh. Come on.
- Hey. Cut it out, you little shit.
But I only made one mistake yesterday!
Hey, there! Yeon Si-eun!
You know
I'm just messing with you.
- And then…
- Let's go.
…somehow, we became seniors.
…gave me her address.
That photo looks great.
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE
WHO UNITED EUNJANG
Who'd vote for him?
After that,
rumors went around
that Baek-jin had disappeared.
No one had any idea…
of where he went.
Will Na Baek-jin…
…find the right answer
to the question he had gotten wrong?
1-0. All by yourself!
What are you spacing out so hard about?
Aah!
Nothing important.
Oh wow, the weather is so nice.
So peaceful.
Hey! My ball. My ball, my ball!
Hello?
Say hi.
♪ Awake ♪
♪ Awakening ♪
♪ From a dream I ♪
♪ Never thought ♪
♪ Would end ♪
You been all right?
Mm-hm.
Who are those guys behind you?
My friends.
That's awesome.
♪ I am dreaming ♪
♪ Now I'm dreaming ♪
♪ For tomorrow, I am here ♪
♪ I can feel everything ♪
♪ And I can go anywhere ♪
♪ I want you to know that… ♪
You're Baek-jin's friend?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Well,
I need Baek-jin's replacement.
CHEONGANG
No child's play
like this bowling club.
Is it fun working for you?
Making money isn't fun. It's hard work.
That doesn't sound very romantic.
By the way, have you…
have you heard from Baek-jin?
I can't get ahold of that fucker.
Who knows?
I'm curious too, kid.
CHEONGANG
THE LATE NA BAEK-JIN